A Finding Aid to the Linda Farris Gallery Records, 1969-1995, in the Archives of American Art AAA.lindfarr
Archives of American Art
- Events files, 1971-1990, undated; Series 4; 0.6 Linear feet Box 9
  - Twentieth Anniversary Events, 1982-1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Herb and Dorothy Vogel Visit, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Reference files, 1969-1994; Series 5; 0.6 Linear feet Box 9-10
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Includes clippings, brochures, booklets, photographs and transparencies, correspondence, and notes. Subjects include collecting contemporary art, soviet artists, photographs of artworks, art controversies, New York art galleries and art world, the Otis Art Institute, modern tapestries, Pioneer Square, potential artists, and Pilchuck Glass School.
  - Art Controversy - New Mexico University Art Gallery, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Collecting Contemporary Art, 1976-1988 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Financial Information, 1974-1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Images, 1973, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Inside New York's Art World Tapes and Films Information, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Modern Master Tapestries, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - New York Art Galleries, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Otis Art Institute, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Artworks, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Photocopied Photographs of Artworks, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pilchuck Glass School, 1981-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
  - Pioneer Square, 1973, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Potential Artists, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Seattle Art Galleries, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Tyler Graphics Ltd., 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - U.S.S.R. Artists, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Financial, Sales and Legal files, 1970-1995; Series 6; 0.4 Linear feet Box 10
  Included in this series are sales records, price lists, receipts, and information on works out of the gallery, including loan and consignment agreements and correspondence.
  - Burns, Marsha - Consignments, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - California Board of Equalization - Sales Tax, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - City of Seattle- City Selects #3 Purchases, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Out of Gallery - Consignments and Loans, 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Price Lists, 1977, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Receipts - Security Pacific National Bank, Saefco, and Seattle First National Bank, 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Sales Records, 1970-1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Work Out of Gallery on Approval / Consignment, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Works Currently on Exhibiton Outside of Gallery, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Linda Farris Papers, 1972-1995; Series 7; 0.9 Linear feet Box 10-11
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by topic.
  This series contains articles by and about Linda Farris and the gallery, clippings, photographs, brochures and flyers, correspondence about arts issues and funding, notes and writings, and a certificate of appreciation for Festival '72 from Seattle Center. Topics covered include the owner's activities and curation outside her own gallery, articles written by Ms. Farris, the ArtFair/Seattle Advisory Committee, the Goodwill Games Visual Arts Subcommittee, the Seattle Art Dealers Association, Ms. Farris's participation in the campaign to keep the Henry Moore sculpture "Vertebrae" in Seattle, an Art for the YWCA project, University of Washington Henry Art Gallery board membership, her involvement in a lecture visit by collectors Herb and Dorothy Vogel, and transcripts of a 1975 Archives of Northwest Art oral history by Sally Swenson, and of a 1989 interview by Ted Rinaldo.
  - ArtFair/Seattle 1992 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - ArtFair/Seattle 1993 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Art/Fair Seattle 1994 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Art/Fair Seattle 1995, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Art/Fair Seattle 1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Articles by Linda Farris, 1981-1989 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Articles by Linda Farris on Collecting Contemporary Art, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Articles by Linda Farris - Series of Three - Notes and Clippings, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28-29)
  - Articles by Linda Farris - Series of Three - Notes and Clippings, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Appreciation - Festival '72, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Clippings and Articles, 1978-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Political, 1975-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Goodwill Games - Arts Festival - Russian Artists, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Goodwill Games Arts Festival, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Goodwill Games - Visual Arts Subcommittee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Henry Gallery University of Washington, 1984-1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Interview by Ted Rinaldo - Transcript, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Moore, Henry - Vertebrae - Campaing to Keep in Seattle, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 12-13)
  - Notes - Speeches and Articles, circa 1970s-1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Oral History by Sally Swenson Transcript - Archives of Northwest Art, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Seattle Art Dealers Association, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - YWCA - Art for, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Printed Materials, 1970-1995; Series 8; 2 Linear feet Box 11-13
  Printed Materials include books, clippings, magazines, press releases, and exhibition announcements, brochures and catalogs, collected by the gallery. Subjects include Isamu Noguchi, Russian art, prints, northwest artists and exhibitions, and architecture.
  - Announcements, Brochures, 1973-1983 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
  - Book - Form and Meaning: Writing on the Renaissance and Modern Art, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Book - Other Sources: An American Essay, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Book - Works on Paper: American Art, 1945-1975, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Book - Seven Stones: A Portrait of Arthur Erickson, Architect, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Book - Isamu Noguchi, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Book - Between Spring and Summer: Soviet Conceptual Arat in the Era of Late Communism, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1974-1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Clippings - Current Magazine, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1981-1988 (Box 12, Folder 6-8)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Magazines, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
  - Magazines, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Magazines, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
  - Magazines, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Magazines, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibition Announcements and Exhibition Catalogs, and Printed Materials from Other Galleries, 1970-1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, and Printed Materials from Other Galleries, 1970-1981 (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
  - Press Releases, 1980-1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)